➵ (ooーeeーoo〜)
➵ Niku, Niku
➵ You can call me Niku
➵ Blue hair, blue tie
➵ Hiding in your wifi
➵ Open Secrets
➵ Anyone can find me
➵ Hear your music running through my mind
➵ I'm thinking Niku, Niku
➵ (ooーeeーoo)
➵ I'm on top of the world because of you
➵ All I wanted to do is follow you
➵ I'll keep singing along with all of you
➵ I'll keep singing along
➵ I'm thinking Niku, Niku
➵ (ooーeeーoo)
➵ Niku, Niku
➵ What's it like to be you ?
➵ 20、20 (Twenty、Twenty)
➵ Looking in a rear-view
➵ Play me, break me, make me feel like Superman
➵ You can do anything you want
➵ I'm on top of the world because of you
➵ All I wanted to do is follow you
➵ I'll keep singing along with all of you
➵ I'll keep singing along
➵ I'm on top of the world because of you
➵ All I wanted to do is follow you
➵ I'll keep singing along with all of you
➵ I'll keep singing along
➵ I'm thinking Niku, Niku
➵ (ooーeeーoo)